guitar-chords.org.uk 2017-12-21

# Guitar-Chords.org.uk - Privacy policy

## Our Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for www.guitar-chords.org.uk**

We take the subject of privacy very seriously and this document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.guitar-chords.org.uk and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.guitar-chords.org.uk makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information that are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

This website does not use cookies, however...

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons through our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Amazon.com.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology that sends information directly to your browser through the advertisements and links that appear on www.guitar-chords.org.uk. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

This web site has no access to, or control over these cookies used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our own privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics to track and measure site behaviour by our users. This helps us understand what our users are looking for on the site, which pages are more popular or may be causing problems. Analytics allows us to find ways improve the site and measure its usefulness to you. We do not collect or have any access to your personal information. Google itself may use analytic data differently. You can find more information about how they use this data and ways in which you can opt out by visiting [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

**Email Addresses**

Generally, we do not collect email addresses or user information. We do have a blog section where you may leave comments. A name and email address is required to use this feature. We aren't interested in it and you may use any made up name and email that you wish to use, we don't require verification. The name and email address that you do use however is stored in a secure database on our website but never used by us for any marketing purposes and never share with third parties.

**Advertising Info**

This website uses advertising and affiliate links to cover its running costs and earn a small profit. You may read more about this here. [Advertising Disclaimer](http://www.guitar-chords.org.uk/disclaimer.html "Advertising")

If you have any further questions regarding our privacy policy you are welcome to contact us by email at [web@guitar-chords.org.uk](mailto:web@guitar-chords.org.uk)
